Guide to the Office of the President Records, Sarah Gibson Blanding Files, 1911-1977 (bulk 1946-1964)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series III. Faculty, 1933-1965
  - English (Folklore), 1949 (Folder 8.34)
  - Officers — English, 1945-1949 (Folder 8.35)
  - Appointments — French, 1945-1949 (Folder 8.36)
  - Officers — French, 1945-1949 (Folder 8.37)
  - Officers — Geography, 1946 (Folder 8.38)
  - Appointments — Geology, 1948 (Folder 8.39)
  - Officers — Geology, 1946-1949 (Folder 8.40)
  - Appointments — German, 1945-1948 (Folder 8.41)
  - Applications Recs. — German, 1946-1947 (Folder 8.42)
  - Officers — German, 1945-1949 (Folder 8.43)
  - Officers — Greek, 1945-1946 (Folder 8.44)
  - Appointments — Health, 1946-1948 (Folder 8.45)
  - Appointment of Psychiatrist, 1947-1949 (Folder 8.46)
  - Health Department (McCurdy Report), 1945-1946 (Folder 8.47)
  - Officers — Health, 1946-1949 (Folder 8.48)
  - Appointments — History, 1946-1948 (Folder 8.49)
  - History Conferences, 1947-1949 (Folder 8.50)
  - Officers — History, 1945-1949 (Folder 8.51)
  - Appointments — Italian, 1948 (Folder 8.52)
  - Officers — Italian, 1945-1946 (Folder 8.53)
  - Officers — Latin, 1946-1949 (Folder 8.54)
  - Appointments — Mathematics, 1946-1948 (Folder 8.55)
  - Officers — Mathematics, 1945-1949 (Folder 8.56)
  - Appointments — Music, 1945-1948 (Folder 8.57)
  - Officers — Music, 1945-1949 (Folder 8.58)
  - Appointments — Philosophy, 1945-1949 (Folder 9.1)
  - Officers — Philosophy, 1945-1949 (Folder 9.2)
  - Appointments — Physical Education, 1946-1949 (Folder 9.3)
  - Officers — Physical Education, 1946-1949 (Folder 9.4)
  - Appointments — Physics, 1945-1947 (Folder 9.5)
  - Officers — Physics, 1945-1949 (Folder 9.6)
  - Appointments — Physiology, 1947-1948 (Folder 9.7)
  - Officers — Physiology, 1945-1948 (Folder 9.8)
  - Appointments — Plant Science, 1948 (Folder 9.9)
  - Officers — Plant Science, 1945-1948 (Folder 9.10)
  - Appointments — Political Science, 1945-1948 (Folder 9.11)
  - Officers — Political Science, 1946-1948 (Folder 9.12)
  - Appointments — Psychology, 1945-1948 (Folder 9.13)
  - Officers — Psychology, 1945-1949 (Folder 9.14)
  - Appointments — Religion, 1946-1948 (Folder 9.15)
  - Officers — Religion, 1945-1948 (Folder 9.16)
  - Appointments — Russian, 1945-1948 (Folder 9.17)
  - Officers — Russian, 1945-1947 (Folder 9.18)
  - Appointments — Spanish, 1946-1947 (Folder 9.19)
  - Officers — Spanish, 1946-1949 (Folder 9.20)
  - Appointments — Zoology, 1947-1948 (Folder 9.21)
  - Officers — Zoology, 1946-1949 (Folder 9.22)
  - Chaplain, 1949-1954 (Folder 9.23)
  - Officers — Dean, 1949-1954 (Folder 9.24)
  - Assistant Dean, 1949-1950 (Folder 9.25)
  - Officers — Committee on Admission, 1949-1954 (Folder 9.26)
  - House Fellows (Mary Conver Mellon), 1951-1952 (Folder 9.27)
  - Director of Scholarships, 1951-1953 (Folder 9.28)
  - Vocational Bureau, 1952-1954 (Folder 9.29)
  - Board of Residents — Warden, 1951 (Folder 9.30)
  - Officers — Warden, 1949-1954 (Folder 9.31)
  - Appointments — Library, 1949-1953 (Folder 9.32)
  - Library (Use of Library outside of Regular Hours), 1953-1954 (Folder 9.33)
  - Officers — Library, 1949-1954 (Folder 9.34)
  - Appointments — Art, 1949-1954 (Folder 9.35)
  - Officers — Art, 1950-1954 (Folder 9.36)
  - Astronomy — Appointments, 1950-1953 (Folder 9.37)
  - Officers — Astronomy, 1949-1954 (Folder 9.38)
  - Appointments — Chemistry, 1950-1954 (Folder 9.39)
  - Officers — Chemistry, 1949-1953 (Folder 9.40)
  - Child Study — Appointments, 1949-1954 (Folder 9.41)
  - Child Study (Project on effects of revised preschool program on personality development and communication efficiency of young children), 1952-1953 (Folder 9.42)
  - Officers — Child Study, 1951-1954 (Folder 9.43)
  - Appointments — Classical Language and Literature, 1953-1954 (Folder 9.44)
  - Classics (Material re Elizabeth C. Evans), 1953-1954 (Folder 9.45)
  - Classics (Material re Mr. Erck’s promotion), 1952 May (Folder 9.46)
  - Officers — Classical Languages and Literature, 1948-1953 (Folder 9.47)
  - Appointments — Drama, 1949-1952 (Folder 9.48)
  - Officers — Drama, 1950-1954 (Folder 9.49)
  - Appointments — Economics, Sociology and Anthropology, 1949-1954 (Folder 9.50)
  - Officers — Economics, Sociology and Anthropology, 1949-1954 (Folder 9.51)
  - Appointments — English, 1949-1954 (Folder 9.52)
  - Mrs. Von Erhardt-Siebold, 1933-1952 (Folder 9.53)
  - Officers — English, 1949-1954 (Folder 9.54)
  - Appointments — French, 1949-1954 (Folder 9.55)
  - French (Mrs. Weber-Marshall), 1946-1951 (Folder 9.56)
  - Officers — French, 1949-1954 (Folder 9.57)
  - Appointments — German, 1950-1953 (Folder 9.58)
  - Applications and Recommendations (German), 1950 (Folder 9.59)
  - Officers — German, 1950-1953 (Folder 9.60)
  - Appointments — Geography, 1951-1952 (Folder 9.61)
  - Officers — Geography, 1951-1954 (Folder 9.62)
  - Appointments — Geology, 1950-1954 (Folder 9.63)
  - Officers — Geology, 1949-1953 (Folder 9.64)
  - Dr. Else Simmel Recommendations, 1949 (Folder 10.1)
  - Appointments — Health, 1949-1950 (Folder 10.2)
  - Officers — Health, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.3)
  - Appointments — History, 1949-1953 (Folder 10.4)
  - Officers — History, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.5)
  - Appointments — Italian, 1949-1952 (Folder 10.6)
  - Italian (Material re Mrs. Pasqualina Manca), 1952-1954 (Folder 10.7)
  - Officers — Italian, 1950-1952 (Folder 10.8)
  - Officers — Mathematics, 1949-1953 (Folder 10.9)
  - Appointments — Music, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.10)
  - Officers — Music, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.11)
  - Appointments — Philosophy, 1949-1953 (Folder 10.12)
  - Philosophy Department — Controversy within Department, 1951 (Folder 10.13)
  - Officers — Philosophy, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.14)
  - Appointments — Physical Education, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.15)
  - Officers — Physical Education, 1950-1954 (Folder 10.16)
  - Appointments — Physics (Communist Accusations), 1949-1953 (Folder 10.17)
  - Officers — Physics, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.18)
  - Appointments — Physiology, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.19)
  - Officers — Physiology, 1952-1954 (Folder 10.20)
  - Appointments — Plant Science, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.21)
  - Officers — Plant Science, 1950-1954 (Folder 10.22)
  - Appointments — Political Science, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.23)
  - Political Science (Middle Eastern Project), 1952-1953 (Folder 10.24)
  - Officers — Political Science, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.25)
  - Psychology — Appointments, 1949-1953 (Folder 10.26)
  - Officers — Psychology, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.27)
  - Appointments — Religion, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.28)
  - Officers — Religion, 1949-1953 (Folder 10.29)
  - Appointments — Russian, 1950-1952 (Folder 10.30)
  - Officers — Russian, 1950-1954 (Folder 10.31)
  - Appointments — Spanish, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.32)
  - Officers — Spanish, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.33)
  - Appointments — Zoology, 1949-1954 (Folder 10.34)
  - Officers — Zoology, 1949-1953 (Folder 10.35)
  - Chaplain, 1955-1956 (Folder 10.36)
  - Dean, 1954-1956 (Folder 10.37)
  - Committee on Admission, 1954-1958 (Folder 10.38)
  - Dean’s Office (Nurses Training), 1953-1954 (Folder 10.39)
  - House Fellows, 1954-1956 (Folder 10.40)
  - Director of Scholarships, 1954-1955 (Folder 10.41)
  - Vocational Bureau, 1954-1955 (Folder 10.42)
  - Warden, 1954-1956 (Folder 10.43)
  - Appointments — Library, 1953-1957 (Folder 10.44)
  - Officers — Library, 1954-1958 (Folder 10.45)
  - Appointments — Art, 1955-1958 (Folder 10.46)
  - Officers — Art, 1955-1957 (Folder 10.47)
  - Officers — Astronomy, 1954-1958 (Folder 10.48)
  - Appointments — Chemistry, 1955-1957 (Folder 10.49)
  - Officers — Chemistry, 1954-1958 (Folder 10.50)
  - Appointments — Child Studies, 1954-1958 (Folder 10.51)
  - Officers — Child Study, 1954-1958 (Folder 10.52)
  - Classics — Appointments, 1956-1958 (Folder 10.53)
  - Officers — Classical Language and Literature, 1955 (Folder 10.54)
  - Appointments — Drama, 1954-1957 (Folder 10.55)
  - Officers — Drama, 1954-1956 (Folder 10.56)
  - Appointments — Economics, Sociology and Anthropology, 1954-1958 (Folder 10.57)
  - Officers — Economics, Sociology and Anthropology, 1954-1958 (Folder 10.58)
  - Appointments — English, 1955-1958 (Folder 10.59)
  - Officers — English, 1954-1958 (Folder 10.60)
  - Appointments — French, 1955-1957 (Folder 10.61)
  - Officers — French, 1954-1958 (Folder 10.62)
  - Officers — Geography, 1956 (Folder 11.1)
  - Officers — Geology, 1954-1956 (Folder 11.2)
  - Geology and Geography — Appointments, 1956-1957 (Folder 11.3)
  - Geology and Geography — Officers, 1956-1957 (Folder 11.4)
  - Appointments — German, 1955-1958 (Folder 11.5)
  - Officers — German, 1954-1956 (Folder 11.6)
  - Appointments – Health, 1954 (Folder 11.7)
  - Officers — Health, 1955-1957 (Folder 11.8)
  - Appointments — History, 1955-1958 (Folder 11.9)
  - History — Committee of Visitors, 1958 (Folder 11.10)
  - Officers — History, 1954-1958 (Folder 11.11)
  - Appointments — Italian, 1955-1956 (Folder 11.12)
  - Officers — Italian, 1955-1956 (Folder 11.13)
  - Mathematics — Appointments, 1956-1957 (Folder 11.14)
  - Officers — Mathematics, 1954-1957 (Folder 11.15)
  - Appointments — Music, 1954-1957 (Folder 11.16)
  - Music (Darlington Collection), 1954-1956 (Folder 11.17)
  - Officers — Music, 1954-1958 (Folder 11.18)
  - Appointments — Philosophy, 1954-1958 (Folder 11.19)
  - Officers — Philosophy, 1955-1957 (Folder 11.20)
  - Appointments — Physical Education, 1954-1958 (Folder 11.21)
  - Officers — Physical Education, 1954-1955 (Folder 11.22)
  - Appointments — Physics, 1954-1958 (Folder 11.23)
  - Officers — Physics, 1954-1957 (Folder 11.24)
  - Appointments — Physiology, 1955-1957 (Folder 11.25)
  - Officers — Physiology, 1954-1957 (Folder 11.26)
  - Appointments — Plant Science, 1955 (Folder 11.27)
  - Officers — Plant Science, 1954-1958 (Folder 11.28)
  - Appointments — Political Science, 1955-1958 (Folder 11.29)
  - Officers — Political Science, 1954-1958 (Folder 11.30)
  - Appointments — Psychology, 1954-1957 (Folder 11.31)
  - Officers — Psychology, 1954-1956 (Folder 11.32)
  - Appointments — Religion, 1955-1957 (Folder 11.33)
  - Officers — Religion, 1955-1956 (Folder 11.34)
  - Appointments — Russian, 1955-1959 (Folder 11.35)
  - Officers — Russian, 1955-1956 (Folder 11.36)
  - Appointments — Spanish, 1956-1957 (Folder 11.37)
  - Appointments — Zoology, 1955-1958 (Folder 11.38)
  - Zoology *material re John George), 1941-1957 (Folder 11.39)
  - Officers — Zoology, 1955-1957 (Folder 11.40)
  - Chaplain, 1958-1959 (Folder 11.41)
  - Chaplain, 1960-1961 (Folder 11.42)
  - Dean, 1958-1959 (Folder 11.43)
  - Dean, 1959-1960 (Folder 11.44)
  - Dean, 1960-1961 (Folder 11.45)
  - Dean of the Faculty, 1961-1962 (Folder 11.46)
  - Dean of the Faculty — Studies re 1962-63 Salary Budget, 1962-1963 (Folder 11.47)
  - Recorder, 1960-1961 (Folder 11.48)
  - House Fellow, 1960-1961 (Folder 11.49)
  - Director of Scholarships, 1960-1961 (Folder 11.50)
  - Vocational Bureau, 1960 (Folder 11.51)
  - Vocational Bureau, 1960-1961 (Folder 11.52)
  - Reorganization of the Dean’s Office, 1960-1961 (Folder 11.53)
  - Dean of Studies, 1961 Jul 1 (Folder 11.54)
  - Assistant Dean, 1961 Jul 1- (Folder 11.55)
  - Vocational Bureau, 1961 (Folder 11.56)
  - Study Counselor, 1961 Jul 1- (Folder 11.57)
  - Scholarships and Financial Aid, 1961 Jul 1- (Folder 11.58)
  - Suggestions for Dean of Studies, 1961 (Folder 11.59)
  - Early Decision Material, 1960-1962 (Folder 11.60)
  - Committee on Admission, 1958-1959 (Folder 11.61)
  - Committee on Admission, 1959-1960 (Folder 11.62)
  - Committee on Admission, 1960-1961 (Folder 11.63)
  - Committee on Admission, 1961 Jul 1- (Folder 11.64)
  - Board of Residents, 1960-1961 (Folder 11.65)
  - Warden, 1958-1960 (Folder 11.66)
  - Warden, 1960-1962 (Folder 11.67)
  - Library — Appointments, 1958-1960 (Folder 11.68)
  - Library — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 11.69)
  - Library (Music), 1962 (Folder 11.70)
  - Library — Centralized Reserve Room, Jun 1961 (Folder 11.71)
  - Library — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 11.72)
  - Library — Officers, 1961-1962 (Folder 11.73)
  - Library — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 11.74)
  - Art — Appointments, 1958-1960 (Folder 11.75)
  - Art — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 11.76)
  - Art Visiting Committee, 1960 (Folder 11.77)
  - Art Department Visiting Committee, 1962 (Folder 11.78)
  - Art — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 11.79)
  - Art — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 11.80)
  - Chemistry — Appointments, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.1)
  - Chemistry — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.2)
  - Chemistry — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.3)
  - Chemistry — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.4)
  - Child Study — Appointments, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.5)
  - Child Study — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.6)
  - Child Study — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.7)
  - Child Study — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.8)
  - Child Study — Officers, 1961-1962 (Folder 12.9)
  - Classics — Appointments, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.10)
  - Classics — Officers, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.11)
  - Classics — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.12)
  - Drama — Appointments, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.13)
  - Drama — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.14)
  - Drama — Applicants, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.15)
  - Drama Department Reorganization, 1962 (Folder 12.16)
  - Drama Visiting Committee, 1960 (Folder 12.17)
  - Drama — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.18)
  - Drama — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.19)
  - Economics, Sociology and Anthropology — Appointments, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.20)
  - Economics, Sociology and Anthropology — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.21)
  - Economics, Sociology and Anthropology — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.22)
  - Economics, Sociology and Anthropology — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.23)
  - English — Appointments, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.24)
  - English — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.25)
  - English — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.26)
  - English — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.27)
  - French — Appointments, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.28)
  - French — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.29)
  - French — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.30)
  - French — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.31)
  - Geology and Geography — Officers, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.32)
  - Geology and Geography — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.33)
  - German — Appointments, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.34)
  - German — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.35)
  - German — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.35)
  - German — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.36)
  - Health — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.37)
  - Psychiatrist (Coeducation), 1959 (Folder 12.38)
  - Health — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.39)
  - History — Appointments, 1959 (Folder 12.40)
  - History — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.41)
  - History — Committee of Visitors, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.42)
  - History — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.43)
  - History — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.44)
  - Italian — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.45)
  - Italian — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.46)
  - Italian — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.47)
  - Mathematics — Appointments, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.48)
  - Mathematics — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.49)
  - Mathematics — Officers, 1959-1960 (Folder 12.50)
  - Mathematics — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.51)
  - Music — Appointments, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.52)
  - Music — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.53)
  - Music — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.54)
  - Music — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.55)
  - Philosophy — Appointments, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.56)
  - Philosophy — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.57)
  - Philosophy — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.58)
  - Philosophy — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.59)
  - Physical Education — Appointments, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.60)
  - Physical Education — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.61)
  - Physical Education — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.62)
  - Physical Education — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.63)
  - Physics — Appointments, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.64)
  - Physics — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.65)
  - Physics — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.66)
  - Physics — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.67)
  - Physiology — Appointments, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.68)
  - Physiology — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.69)
  - Physiology — Officers, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.70)
  - Physiology — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.71)
  - Plant Science — Appointments, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.72)
  - Plant Science — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.73)
  - Plant Science — Officers, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.74)
  - Plant Science — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.75)
  - Political Science — Appointments, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.76)
  - Political Science — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.77)
  - Political Science Middle East Program, 1959 (Folder 12.78)
  - Political Science — Officers, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.79)
  - Political Science — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.80)
  - Psychology — Appointments, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.81)
  - Psychology — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.82)
  - Psychology — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.83)
  - Psychology — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.84)
  - Religion — Appointments, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.85)
  - Religion — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.86)
  - Religion — Officers, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.87)
  - Religion — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.88)
  - Russian — Appointments, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.89)
  - Russian — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.90)
  - Russian — Applicants, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.91)
  - Russian — Officers, 1958-1960 (Folder 12.92)
  - Russian — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.93)
  - Spanish — Appointments, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.94)
  - Spanish — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.95)
  - Spanish — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.96)
  - Zoology — Appointments, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.97)
  - Zoology — Appointments, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.98)
  - Zoology — Officers, 1958-1959 (Folder 12.99)
  - Zoology — Officers, 1960-1961 (Folder 12.100)
  - Chaplain, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.1)
  - Recorder, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.2)
  - House Fellows, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.3)
  - Director of Elementary Education, 1964-1965 (Folder 13.4)
  - Dean of Faculty, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.5)
  - Dean of Studies, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.6)
  - Committee on Selection of Dean of Studies, 1965 (Folder 13.7)
  - Director of Scholarships, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.8)
  - Assistant Dean, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.9)
  - Dean of Freshmen, 1964-1965 (Folder 13.10)
  - Study Counselor, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.11)
  - Vocational Bureau, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.12)
  - Dean of Residence, 1964-1965 (Folder 13.13)
  - Admissions Office — Applicants, 1964-1965 (Folder 13.14)
  - Committee on Admission, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.15)
  - Board of Residents, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.16)
  - Warden, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.17)
  - Library (Music), 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.18)
  - Library — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.19)
  - Art — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.20)
  - Art — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 (Folder 13.21)
  - Biology — Officers, 1964-1965 (Folder 13.22)
  - Chemistry — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.23)
  - Chemistry — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.24)
  - Child Study — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.25)
  - Child Study — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.26)
  - Classics — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 (Folder 13.27)
  - Drama Department Visiting Committee, 1963-1964 (Folder 13.28)
  - Drama — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.29)
  - Economics Candidates, Apr 1964 (Folder 13.30)
  - Economics, Sociology and Anthropology — Applicants, 1964-1965 (Folder 13.31)
  - Anthropology Candidates (Open File), 1963 (Folder 13.32)
  - Anthropology Candidates Instructor Position, 1963 (Folder 13.33)
  - Economics, Sociology, Anthropology — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.34)
  - Economics, Sociology and Anthropology [Confidential], 1963 (Folder 13.35)
  - English — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.36)
  - English — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.37)
  - French — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.38)
  - French — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.39)
  - Geology and Geography — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.40)
  - Geology and Geography — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.41)
  - German — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.42)
  - German Department [Confidential], 1962-1965 (Folder 13.43)
  - German — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.44)
  - Health — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.45)
  - Medical — Consultant File, 1962-1963 (Folder 13.46)
  - Health Department — Psychiatrist, 1962-1963 (Folder 13.47)
  - Health — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.48)
  - History — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.49)
  - History — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 13.50)
  - Italian — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.1)
  - Italian — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.2)
  - Mathematics — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.3)
  - Mathematics — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.4)
  - Madrigal Group Trip, 1965 (Folder 14.5)
  - Music — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.6)
  - Organs, 1962-1963 (Folder 14.7)
  - Philosophy — Applicants, 1964-1965 (Folder 14.8)
  - Philosophy — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.9)
  - Physical Education — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.10)
  - Physical Education — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.11)
  - Physics — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.12)
  - Physics — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.13)
  - Physiology — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.14)
  - Plant Science — Appointments, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.15)
  - Plant Science — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.16)
  - Political Science — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.17)
  - Political Science — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.18)
  - Psychology — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.19)
  - Psychology — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.20)
  - Religion — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.21)
  - Religion — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.22)
  - Russian — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.23)
  - Special Russian Language Program, 1962-1964 (Folder 14.24)
  - Russian — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.25)
  - Spanish — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.26)
  - Zoology — Applicants, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.27)
  - Zoology — Officers, 1962 Jul 1 - (Folder 14.28)
- Series IV. Gifts, 1926-1969
  - Gifts (General) and Anonymous, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.29)
  - Gifts — A, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.30)
  - Gifts — B, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.31)
  - Gifts — C, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.32)
  - Gifts — D, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.33)
  - Gifts — E, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.34)
  - Gifts — F, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.35)
  - Gifts — G, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.36)
  - Gifts — H, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.37)
  - Gifts — I, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.38)
  - Gifts — J, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.39)
  - Gifts — K, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.40)
  - Gifts — L, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.41)
  - Gifts — M, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.42)
  - Gifts — N, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.43)
  - Gifts — O, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.44)
  - Gifts — P, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.45)
  - Gifts — Q, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1; (empty) (Folder 14.46)
  - Gifts — R, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.47)
  - Gifts — S, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.48)
  - Gifts — T, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.49)
  - Gifts — U, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.50)
  - Gifts — V, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.51)
  - Gifts — W, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.52)
  - Gifts — X, Y, Z, 1962 Jul 1 – 1964 Jul 1 (Folder 14.53)
  - Administration Building, 1954 (Folder 15.1)
  - Alumnae House (Coonley and Hooker), 1949-1953 (Folder 15.2)
  - Phebe H. Beadle Fund for Scientific Departments, 1950-1963 (Folder 15.3)
  - William Bingham II Scholarship Fund, 1956-1961 (Folder 15.4)